Lesson 44. Speed and comfort. People traveling long distances frequently have to decide whether they would prefer to go by land.
第44课。速度和舒适。长途旅行的人经常必须决定是否宁愿陆路去。
positively: adv. 绝对地，完全地
See, or air. Hardly anyone can positively enjoy sitting in a train for more than a few hours.
看到或空气。几乎没有人可以积极喜欢坐在火车上超过几个小时。
compartment: n.   列车客车厢内的分隔间（或单间）, cramped: adj. 窄小的, stuffy: adj. 憋气的，闷气的
Train compartments soon get cramped and stuffy. It is almost impossible to take your mind off the journey.
火车舱很快就会局促和闷闷不乐。几乎不可能摆脱旅程。
monotonous: adj. 枯燥的，乏味的, rhythm: n.   有节奏的运动, click: v.   发出咔哒声, lull: v.   催人欲睡
Reading is only a partial solution. For the monotonous rhythm of the wheels clicking on the rails soon lulls you to sleep.
阅读只是部分解决方案。对于轮子的单调节奏，单击栏杆很快就会让您入睡。
snatch: n.   短时，片段
During the day, sleep comes in snatches. At night, when you really wish to go to sleep, you rarely manage to do so.
白天，睡眠有抢夺。到了晚上，当您真的想睡觉时，您很少设法这样做。
sleeper: n.   卧铺
If you are lucky enough to get a sleeper, you spend half the night staring at the small blue light in the ceiling.
如果您很幸运能够让卧铺者望去，那么您将半夜盯着天花板上的小蓝色灯。
inspection: n.   检查
Or fumbling to find you ticket for inspection.
或摸索寻找检查票。
destination: n.   目的地, exhaust: v.   使精疲力尽
Inevitably you arrive at your destination almost exhausted. Long car journeys are even less pleasant.
您不可避免地到达目的地几乎筋疲力尽。长途旅行甚至不那么愉快。
motorway: n.   快车道
For it is quite impossible even to read. On motorways you can, at least, travel fairly safely at high speeds.
因为即使阅读也是完全不可能的。在高速公路上，您至少可以高速行驶。
But more often than not, the greater part of the journey is spent on roads with few service stations and too much traffic.
但是，通常，旅程的大部分时间都花在服务站很少和交通过多的道路上。
ferry: n.   渡船, cruise: n.   巡游船, civilize: v.   使文明
By comparison, ferry trips or cruises offer a great variety of civilized comforts.
相比之下，渡轮旅行或游轮提供各种文明的舒适感。
spacious: adj. 宽敞的
You can stretch your legs on the spacious decks. Play games. Meet interesting people and enjoy good food. Always assuming.
您可以在宽敞的甲板上伸展双腿。玩游戏。结识有趣的人并享受美食。总是假设。
seasick: adj. 晕船的
Of course, that the sea is calm. If it is not, and you are likely to get seasick, no form of transport could be worse.
当然，大海很平静。如果不是，并且您可能会晕船，那么运输的形式可能会更糟。
Even if you travel in ideal weather. Sea journeys take a long time. Relatively few people are prepared to sacrifice holiday time for the pleasure of traveling by sea.
即使您在理想的天气下旅行。海上旅行需要很长时间。相对较少的人准备牺牲假期，以享受海上旅行的乐趣。
intimidate: v.   恐吓，恫吓
Aeroplanes have the reputation of being dangerous and even hardened travelers are intimidated by.
飞机的声誉是被危险，甚至是坚强的旅行者都被吓倒了。
disadvantage: n.   短处，缺点
Them, they also have the disadvantage of being an expensive form of transport.
他们，他们也有一种昂贵的运输形式的缺点。
exhilarating: adj. 使人高兴的，令人兴奋的
But nothing can match them for speed and comfort. Traveling at a height of 30,000 feet, far above the clouds, and at over 500 miles an hour is an exhilarating experience.
但是没有什么可以匹配它们的速度和舒适。以30,000英尺的高度行驶，远远超过云端，每小时超过500英里，这是一种令人振奋的体验。
You do not have to devise ways of taking your mind off the journey.
您不必设计方法来摆脱困境。
destination: n.   目的地
For an aeroplane gets you to your destination rapidly. For a few hours, you settle back in a deep armchair to enjoy the flight.
对于飞机，您可以迅速到达目的地。几个小时以来，您就会坐在深扶手椅上享受飞行。
escapist: n.   逍遥者, champagne: n.   香槟洒
The real escapist can watch a film and sip champagne on some services.
真正的逃避现实者可以看电影并在某些服务中饮香槟。
refinement: n.   精心的安排
But even when such refinements are not available, there is plenty to keep you occupied.
但是，即使没有这种改进，也有很多可以让您占领的。
An aeroplane offers you an unusual and breathtaking view of the world.
飞机为您提供了世界上不寻常而令人叹为观止的景色。
soar: v.   高飞，翱翔, effortlessly: adv. 不费力地
You soar effortlessly over high mountains and deep valleys. You really see the shape of the land.
您毫不费力地在高山和深山谷上飞翔。您真的看到了土地的形状。
landscape: n.   景色
If the landscape is hidden from view, you can enjoy the extraordinary sight of unbroken cloud planes that stretch out for miles before you.
如果隐藏了景观，您可以欣赏到不间断的云飞机的非凡景象，这些飞机在您之前延伸了几英里。
While the sun shines brilliantly in a clear sky, the journey is so smooth that there is nothing to prevent you from reading or sleeping.
虽然阳光在晴朗的天空中闪耀着，但旅程是如此顺利，以至于没有什么可以阻止您阅读或睡觉的。
destination: n.   目的地, fresh: adj. 精神饱满的, uncrumpled: adj. 没有垮下来
However you decide to spend your time. One thing is certain. You will arrive at your destination fresh and uncrumpled.
但是，您决定花时间。一件事是肯定的。您将到达目的地，新鲜而浮出水面。
You will not have to spend the next few days recovering from a long and arduous journey.
您将不必在接下来的几天里从漫长而艰巨的旅程中恢复过来。